A Guide to the 1930-1999
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Schools, Colleges and Universities 1948-1993
  - University of Richmond n.d. 1983-1988 (Box 72)
  - University of Richmond 1989-1993 (Box 72)
  - University of Richmond 1990-1991 (Box 72)
  - University of Richmond Founder's Dinner 1986 (Box 72)
  - University of Richmond Douglas Southall Freeman Hall 1965 (Box 72)
  - University of Richmond Freeman Society 1975 (Box 72)
  - University of Richmond Self-Management Workshop 1979 (Box 72)
  - University of Richmond Women's Resource Center 1990 (Box 72)
  - University of Richmond Women's Resource Center, includes speech by MTC, What Women Can do3/16/91 (Box 72)
  - Westhampton College 1977 (Box 73)
  - University of Virginia-Bobby Blake Fund 1984 (Box 73)
  - Vassar College n.d. 1935-1940 (Box 73)
  - Vassar College 1962-1968 (Box 73)
  - Vassar College 1986-1992 (Box 73)
  - Vassar College 1992 (Box 73)
  - Vassar College-Classroom Notes (Box 73)
  - Vassar College 50th Reunion 1982-1987 (Box 73)
  - VCU- Behind the Headlines2/17/84 (Box 73)
  - VCU Center for Public Affairs 1982 (Box 73)
  - VCU Richmond Revitalization Program, Broad Street Residential Study: Living Over the Store1986 (Box 73)
  - VCU Richmond Revitalization Program Commentary by MTC in Revitalization NewsNov. 1983 (Box 73)
  - VCU Richmond Revitalization Program Revitalization News, newsletter 1983-1988 (Box 73)
  - VCU-Summer Writer's Workshop 1987-1988 (Box 74)
  - VCU-Writer's Workshop, VCU 8/10-23/1988 (Box 74)
  - VCU-Medical College of Virginia (Box 74)
  - VCU-MCV Foundation 1990 (Box 74)
  - VCU-MCV Kendig Chair 1989-1991 (Box 74)
  - Virginia Military Institute 1980 (Box 74)
  - Washington and Lee University 1977-1985 (Box 74)
  - Washington and Lee University 11/7/86 (Box 74)
  - Washington and Lee University 1987-1993 (Box 74)
  - Washington and Lee University, Lenfest Center for the Performing Arts, Included photos and slides 1991 (Box 74)
- St. Paul's Episcopal Church 1937-1993
  - St. Paul's Episcopal Church 1955-1956 (Box 75)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal Church 1980-1982 (Box 75)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal Church 1980-1982 (Box 75)
  - Bible Class 1985 (Box 75)
  - Buildings and Memorials Advisory Committee 1982-1983 (Box 75)
  - Canvas 1982 (Box 75)
  - Caring Tree 1991 (Box 75)
  - Carignan, Rev. Shanda H.H.-Sermons by Carignan (Box 75)
  - College Party 12/17/86 (Box 75)
  - Diocesan Committee on Social Responsibility (Box 75)
  - Episcopal Churchwomen 1983, 1986 (Box 75)
  - Gibson, Bishop Robert Fisher-Dinner 5/4/84 (Box 75)
  - Hospital Visiting Committee (Box 75)
  - Hymnal Revision 1982 (Box 75)
  - Journal of Lenton Meditations 1991 (Box 76)
  - Kilmarnock Episcopal Churchwoman talk 3/2/87 (Box 76)
  - Lee, Bishop Peter James-Fund for World Relief 12/3/91 (Box 76)
  - Lenton Luncheons (Box 76)
  - Newsletter 1982 (Box 76)
  - Parish House 1961 (Box 1961)
  - Party-150th Anniversary (Box 76)
  - Racial Study Commission, n.d. (Box 76)
  - Racial Study Commission 1958-1961 (Box 76)
  - Racial Study Commission-Reports, Publications 1937-1960 (Box 76)
  - Racial Study Commission The Race Problem and the Church (Box 76)
  - Reupholstering Committee 1961-1962 (Box 76)
  - Spong, John and Joan n.d. 1969-1970 (Box 76)
  - Spong, The Rev. John S. 1974-1976 (Box 76)
  - Spong, Bishop John S. clippings and sermons (Box 76)
  - Stewardship Committee 1981-1984 (Box 77)
  - Survey 1981 (Box 77)
  - Talk 12/6/92 (Box 77)
  - Thanksgiving Litany (Box 77)
  - Vestry 1991 (Box 77)
  - Vestry 1992 (Box 77)
  - Vestry (1 of 2) 1993 (Box 77)
  - Vestry (2 of 2) 1993 (Box 78)
  - Vestry Party 1/23/83 (Box 78)
  - Women of St. Paul's Study Committee (Box 78)
  - Women's Auxiliary-Education-Isaiah 1958 (Box 78)
  - Women's Auxiliary-Notes on the Gospel of St. Mark (Box 78)
  - Worship Board 1975 (Box 78)
- Alphabetical Files 1935-1994
  - All I Ever Really Needed to Know, I Learned in Kindergarten-clipping (Box 79)
  - Alliance Francaise 1979 (Box 79)
  - American Federation of Art Trustees Tea 1986 (Box 79)
  - American Red Cross-Advisory Comm. Party 10/27/92 (Box 79)
  - American Society of Interior Designers 1981 (Box 79)
  - Artbags-735 Madison Ave. (Box 79)
  - Aspen 1984 (Box 79)
  - Aspen 1985 (Box 79)
  - Aspen 1986 (Box 79)
  - Aspen 1987 (Box 79)
  - Aspen 1988 (Box 79)
  - Aspen Co. 1990 (Box 79)
  - Atlantic Council of the United States 1985 (Box 79)
  - Bal du Bois, Presented by the Junior Board of the Sheltering Arms Hospital 1973 (Box 79)
  - Baltimore Museum of Art 1985 (Box 79)
  - Baltimore Museum of Art-Inaugural Exhibition 1982 (Box 79)
  - Barlett Tree Expert Co. (Box 79)
  - Beyond the Road Less Traveled-Scott Peck (Box 79)
  - Bicycles (Box 79)
  - Bill of Rights-200th Anniversary (Box 79)
  - Billboards 1988-1990 (Box 79)
  - Black and White in Richmond 1981 (Box 79)
  - Brussels World's Fair 1958 (Box 79)
  - The Business Enterprise Trust 1958 (Box 79)
  - Butler's Schedule n.d. (Box 79)
  - Camphill Village, U.S.A. Inc. 1968 (Box 80)
  - Calendar (MTC Calendar-documents daily schedule 1988, oversize (Box 80)
  - Callers n.d. (Box 80)
  - Canterbury Cathedral Trust (Box 80)
  - Cary Street Woodworks (Box 80)
  - Cathedral of the Sacred Heart (Box 80)
  - Caucus for the Future of Central Virginia 1992 (Box 80)
  - Center for Palladian Studies in America 1983 (Box 80)
  - Charitable Appeals 1943 (Box 80)
  - ChemLawn (Box 80)
  - Children's Festival Committee 1990 (Box 80)
  - Chilton, Samuel Blackwell-Grace and Holy Trinity Church 1960 (Box 80)
  - China 1989 (Box 80)
  - Chinese Rug (Information given by Merrill Moore) (Box 80)
  - Christ Church, Gordonsville, Va-Women's Auxilary 1961 (Box 80)
  - Christmas Pageant 12/24/82 (Box 80)
  - Christmas Party 12/26/76 (Box 80)
  - Christmas Party 12/26/78 (Box 80)
  - Christmas Party 12/26/79 (Box 80)
  - Christmas Party 1980 (Box 80)
  - Christmas Party 12-26-80 (Box 80)
  - Christmas Party 1981 (Box 80)
  - Christmas Party 1982 (Box 80)
  - Christmas Party 1983 (Box 81)
  - Christmas Party 1984 (Box 81)
  - Christmas Party 1986 (Box 81)
  - Christmas Party 1987 (Box 81)
  - Christmas Party 1988 (Box 81)
  - Christmas Party 1989 (Box 81)
  - Christmas Party 1990 (Box 81)
  - Christian Children's Fund 1991 (Box 81)
  - Church Women United 1989 (Box 81)
  - Churchill's Visits to Virginia 1991 (Box 81)
  - Citizens for Public Radio 1986 (Box 81)
  - City Planning-New Haven Citizens Action Commission Annual Report 1958 (Box 81)
  - Civil War Series 1990 (Box 81)
  - Cleaning Upholstery (Box 81)
  - Coiffures (Box 81)
  - Community Learning Week 1981-1983 (Box 82)
  - Coummunity Learning Week 1985 (Box 82)
  - The Confederate Museum-visit to Houston, Tx April 1987 (Box 82)
  - Confederate Navy 1987 (Box 82)
  - Continental Cable Firm 1986 (Box 82)
  - Corcoran Gallery of Art 1945 (Box 82)
  - Culver 1990 (Box 82)
  - Daughters of Cincinnati (Box 82)
  - Pierre Teilhord De Chardin, Phenomenon of Man Project (Box 82)
  - Debutante Party 1959 (Box 82)
  - Debutante Party 1960 (Box 82)
  - Dedication of Lee and Jackson Statue, Baltimore, MD 1948, 1983 (Box 82)
  - Diets (Box 82)
  - Dillon, C. Douglas n.d. 1961 (Box 82)
  - Disney in Virginia 1994 (Box 82)
  - Domestic Staff 1960-1963 (Box 82)
  - Dominion Bankshares Corporation-Child Care Program 1990 (Box 82)
  - Elk Hill Farm 1990 (Box 82)
  - English Heart Care 1959 (Box 82)
  - English Speaking Union House Tour 4/14/81 (Box 82)
  - Eyeglasses, MTC 1971, 1986 (Box 82)
  - Family and Children's Trust Fund of Virginia 1990-1991 (Box 82)
  - Farmington Cookbook 1974 (Box 82)
  - Fence 1984 (Box 82)
  - Fine Arts, notes on 1938-1939 (Box 82)
  - First Presbyterian Church 4/7/81 (Box 82)
  - First Presbyterian Church 1/6/87 (Box 82)
  - For Young People Only-Kweli Leopart 1984 (Box 82)
  - Friend of the Executive Mansion Award (Box 82)
  - Friends of the Winterhur 1977-1984 (Box 82)
  - Future Ideas for 1987 (Box 82)
  - Garden 1976 (Box 83)
  - Garden 1979-1983, oversize (Box 83)
  - Garden 1987-1989 (Box 83)
  - Garden--Gray, Martha n.d. 1987-1991 (Box 83)
  - Garden Party 4/30/83 (Box 83)
  - Garden Club Dinner 10/4/83 (Box 83)
  - General Assembly Commendation 2/22/91 (Box 83)
  - Ginter Park Presbyterian Church 12/18/88 (Box 83)
  - Ginter Park Woman's Club-3016 Seminary Ave 2/3/87 (Box 83)
  - Glasgow, Ellen newsletter 1983-1988 (Box 83)
  - Golden Book (Box 83)
  - News Articles about Goodness 1968, 1981 (Box 83)
  - Grace and Holy Trinity 1989 (Box 83)
  - Grace and Holy Trinity Church Retreat 10/17/87 (Box 83)
  - Grand Circle, GCT Travel (Box 83)
  - Greek Orthodox Cathedral 75th Anniversary 1991-1992 (Box 83)
  - Gun Control 1993 (Box 83)
  - Guthrie Party 5/23/84 (Box 83)
  - Hamner, Earl Jr. 1973, 1987 (Box 84)
  - Hearing Hands 1984 (Box 84)
  - Herb Class 1982 (Box 84)
  - Historic Christ Church 5/16/91 (Box 84)
  - Hill, Haywood N. This I Believe reprint of statement on race in the South 1961, 1964 (Box 84)
  - Hollywood Cemetery 1967-1978 (Box 84)
  - Hospital Stay, Visitors 8/2/73-9/8/73 (Box 84)
  - Jewish Woman's Club 1992 (Box 84)
  - Jamestown Festival 1957 (Box 84)
  - Jamestown Settlers 1989-1990 (Box 84)
  - Japanese 2/25/69 (Box 84)
  - Jefferson Bust (Box 84)
  - Juvenile Problems-Correspondence articles 1950s-1960s (Box 84)
  - Kiwanian Builder Committee 1990-1991 (Box 84)
  - Knoll-Shu Party 11/15/88 (Box 84)
  - Kwanza-Janine Bell 1991-1992 (Box 84)
  - Landscapping (Box 84)
  - Le Cercle Francais 1964 (Box 84)
  - Legal Aid 1991 (Box 84)
  - Liberty Bell Award 1991 (Box 84)
  - Linus Pauling Institute of Science and Medicine 1979-1980 (Box 84)
  - Living Room Redecoration 1984-1985 (Box 84)
  - Lord Esher, remarks by Esher, Williamsburg, Va 1956 (Box 84)
  - Magazine Subscriptions 1943-1944 (Box 84)
  - Maggie Walker Statue 1988 (Box 84)
  - Main Street Station 1986 (Box 84)
  - Massey Cance Center 1989 (Box 84)
  - Media General 1985-1990 (Box 84)
  - Menus and Recipes n.d. 1956-1961 (Box 85)
  - Metropolitan Richmond-Convention and Visitors Bureau News (Box 85)
  - Monumental Church n.d. (Box 85)
  - Morris, Philip Southern Living1989 (Box 85)
  - Museum Directors 1961 (Box 85)
  - Museum of the Confederacy n.d. (Box 85)
  - Nashville in Town and CountryMay 1965 (Box 85)
  - National Anthem 1990 (Box 85)
  - National Arbor Day (Box 85)
  - National Gallery of Art 1985 (Box 85)
  - National Park Service- 75th Anniversary 1991 (Box 85)
  - Needlepoint-Article on n.d. (Box 85)
  - Olmstead, Frederick Law Anotable Lawsuit1973 (Box 85)
  - Opera in Richmond 1986 (Box 85)
  - Opera Society of Washington 1958-1959 (Box 85)
  - Other People's Speeches n.d. 1980, 1982 (Box 85)
  - Our Town-WXEX News n.d. (Box 85)
  - Oxmoor House 1982 (Box 85)
  - Paideia Proposal 1983-1987 (Box 85)
  - Palladian Society Weekend May 1982 (Box 85)
  - Parties-At home-Cocktail 1960 (Box 86)
  - Parties-At home-Caldwell Luncheon 1960 (Box 86)
  - Parties-At home-Houghton Luncheon 1960 (Box 86)
  - Parties-At home-Fellow's Dinner 1964 (Box 86)
  - Parties-At home-Family 1960 (Box 86)
  - Parties-Book and Author 1970 (Box 86)
  - Parties-Christmas (Elizabeth Cheek) 1971 (Box 86)
  - Parties-Dinner Party 6/22/35 (Box 86)
  - Parties-Dinner Parties (Box 86)
  - Parties-Harvard Party 3/29/82 (Box 86)
  - Parties-Higgins (Box 86)
  - Parties-Huldah's (29 and 30) 1971 (Box 86)
  - Parties-Kennedy Center 1971 (Box 86)
  - Parties-Rawles Party 1984 (Box 86)
  - Parties-Va Museum Staff 1971 (Box 86)
  - Parties-John White-Farewell Party 6/5/61 (Box 86)
  - People Helping People 1987 (Box 87)
  - Pembroke-Map of Pembroke-Richmond, Va 1984, oversize (Box 87)
  - Personal (Box 87)
  - Phillip Morris-USA (Box 87)
  - Pineapple Symbol (history of) 1964 (Box 87)
  - Planters Bank Building 1966-1982 (Box 87)
  - Porcelain in the Age of Mozart (Chrysler Museum) 1984 (Box 87)
  - Prayer Breakfast 1982 (Box 87)
  - Prophecy 1980 (Box 87)
  - Providence Park Baptist Church--25th Anniversary of Dr. Miles Jerome Jones, Pastor 1988 (Box 87)
  - Queen Elizabeth II 1957 (Box 87)
  - Race Relations, Ideas on (Box 87)
  - Racism--WCVE Town Meeting 11-17-94 (Box 87)
  - Richmond Black Student Foundation 1985-1986 (Box 87)
  - Richmond Public Library-Friends of the Library 1959-1961 (Box 87)
  - Royal Wedding (Box 87)
  - St. James' Adult Forum 11/2/88 (Box 87)
  - St. Peter's Church, Oysterville, MA n.d. 1982-1989 (Box 87)
  - St. Peter's Church, Oysterville, MA-Cross Keys Newsletter 1983-1990 (Box 87)
  - St. Stephen's Church 1984-1985 (Box 87)
  - Science Museum of Virginia (Box 87)
  - Skywatch (Box 88)
  - Statue of Liberty (Box 88)
  - Studio Theatre of Richmond (Box 88)
  - Style Magazine (Box 88)
  - Scotland (Box 88)
  - Seed Order 1965 (Box 88)
  - Segregation-newspaper clippings, periodicals late 1950's (Box 88)
  - Sermons 1988 (Box 88)
  - Service and Kind Assistance (Box 88)
  - Service Plates (Box 88)
  - Service Plates (Box 88)
  - Skylark Farm, Vegetable and Flower Garden Layout for Year 1976, oversize (Box 88)
  - Thailand (Box 88)
  - Travel n.d. 1968 (Box 88)
  - Trees for Richmond-Luncheon 3/27/92 (Box 88)
  - Trolleys (Box 88)
  - Virginia Beach-Vacation 1961 (Box 88)
  - Virginia Cavalcade article by MTC on the Virginia Room at the 1939 World's Fair 1985 (Box 88)
  - Virginia Women History (Box 88)
  - V.O.I.C.E-Visions Organized for Informed Community Expression 1981-1983 (Box 88)
  - Warner, Alice Sizer- Bethany (Box 88)
  - Wells Cathedral 1978 (Box 88)
  - Westminster Presbyterian Church 6/8/88 (Box 88)
  - Westmoreland Place: Reynolds Property 1982-1985 (Box 88)
  - Westwood Baptist Church 1961 (Box 88)
  - Wianno Club 1980-1981 (Box 88)
  - Wianno Club Receipts 1981 (Box 89)
  - Wianno Club, Cape Cod, Mass. Vacation 1982 (Box 89)
  - Williamsburg, VA Thanksgiving Weekend 1977 (Box 89)
  - Williamsburg Trips 1979 (Box 89)
  - Wilson, Edmund By Dark Cocytus Shore from The New Yorker (Box 89)
  - Wintherthur Trip 1978 (Box 89)
  - Woodlands Plantation (Box 89)
  - WRFK 1986 (Box 89)
  - Yale Club 1940 (Box 89)
  - YWCA 1938 (Box 89)
  - Yale Art Associates and Cocktail Party 1980 (Box 89)
  - Application for Certifications an SBA Section 508 Certified Document, oversize (Box 90)
  - Calendar (MTC's Calendar-documents daily schedule) 1988, oversize (Box 90)
  - Downtown Plan: First Draft 1984, oversize (Box 90)
  - Pembroke-Map of Pembroke-Richmond, Va 1984, oversize (Box 90)
  - Photographic reproduction of Virginia Statue for Religious Freedom plaque at State Capitol, oversize (Box 90)
  - Skylark Farm, Vegetable and Flower Garder Layout for Year, oversize (Box 90)
  - Correspondence (1 of 3) 1931-1964 (Box 91)
  - Correspondence n.d. (2 of 3) 1986-1988 (Box 91)
  - Correspondence (3 of 3) (Box 91)
  - Acheson, Alice 1991 (Box 91)
  - Adler, Ann (Adler Family) 1960's-1970's (Box 91)
  - Adler, Ann, (Adler Family) (1 of 2) 1980's (Box 91)
  - Adler, Ann, (Adler Family) (2 of 2) 1980's (Box 91)
  - Adler, Ann, (Addler Family) 1990-1991 (Box 91)
  - Adler, Morimer and Caroline, (2 of 2) (Box 91)
  - Adler-Malhotra Wedding 1988 (Box 91)
  - Adler, Mortimer and Caroline, n.d., (1 of 2) 1977, 1979-1980, 1982-1987 (Box 91)
  - Albee, Edward 1963-1971 (Box 91)
  - Allen, Governor George 1994-1995 (Box 91)
  - Applewhite, Hunter n.d. 1988-1989, 1991, 1993 (Box 91)
  - Asch, Andrew J. Jr. (Christopher Newport Park) 1985-1986 (Box 91)
  - Ashworth, Mary Wells Memorial, n.d. 1992-1993 (Box 91)
  - Bailey, Bill 1989 (Box 91)
  - Ballentine, Mary Ballou (Box 91)
  - Banks, Mary n.d. (Box 91)
  - Barzun, Jacques 1959 (Box 91)
  - Bayne, Bishop Stephen F., Jr. 1958 (Box 91)
  - Beinecke, Mr and Mrs. Frederick W. 1965 (Box 91)
  - Bemiss, Mr and Mrs. Samuel (Doreen) 1957-1966 (Box 91)
  - Benedetti, Joseph B 1989 (Box 91)
  - Berry Hill 1996 (Box 91)
  - Beverley, Bruce 1990 (Box 91)
  - Beyer, Donald S. Jr. 1989-1990, 1992-1993, 1995-1998 (Box 91)
  - Biddle, Craig and Neil, n.d. 1980, 1983-1985, 1988-1991, 1997 (Box 91)
  - Bissell, Mr. and Mrs. Frank (Nellie Merrick), n.d. (Box 91)
  - Blake 1967, 1969 (Box 91)
  - Block, Leigh and Mary 1967 (Box 91)
  - Blunt, Ruth Homes 1968-1970 (Box 91)
  - Bobb, Robert, n.d. 1989-1991 (Box 91)
  - Bobb, Robert, n.d. 1989-1991 (Box 91)
  - Boel 1964 (Box 91)
  - Boothe 1961 (Box 91)
  - Bowie, Marian M. (Mrs) 1974, 1978, 1980-1981, 1983-1987, 1990, 1992 (Box 91)
  - Branch, Mel n.d. (Box 91)
  - Brawley, Norma (Mrs. Fransis W. P. Brawley) 1989 (Box 91)
  - Karen Germaine and Austin Brockenbrough Wedding (incl other Ephfmera trip) August 1994 (Box 91)
  - Books, Mrs Edward (Markell) n.d. (Box 91)
  - George, Brooks Chair 1989-1990 (Box 91)
  - Brown, Bishop amd Mrs. R, n.d. (Box 91)
  - Brown, J. Carter 1992 (Box 91)
  - Brown, Mr. and Mrs John Nicholas (Anne) 1956-1967 (Box 91)
  - Brown, Phyllis Coghill, n.d. 1982, 1993, 1995-1996 (Box 91)
  - Bryan, D. Tennant (Clippings Correspondence), various dates (Box 91)
  - Bryan, Jane Norton 1954-1957 (Box 91)
  - Bryan, Joe and Jacqueline 1962-1988 (Box 91)
  - Bryan, Joseph III, 1981-1993 (Box 91)
  - Burke, Mrs. Jackson 1993 (Box 91)
  - Burwell 1934 (Box 91)
  - Bush, Madge Morgan (Box 91)
  - Callery, Mary n.d. (Box 91)
  - Capps, Jane (Mrs. Thomas E.) 303 Long Lane, Richmond 23221, n.d. 1989-1992 (Box 91)
  - Carey, Juliet, 1990 (Box 91)
  - Carmody, Penny Powell, n.d. 1991 (Box 91)
  - Carter, Elizabeth Reed 1955 (Box 91)
  - ?, Charlie 1935 (Box 91)
  - Chisholm, Margaret Ann 1991 (Box 91)
  - Christmas, Eric and Donna 1967 (Box 91)
  - Christy, David Stewart and Anita 1993 (Box 91)
  - Clark, Michael 1988 (Box 91)
  - Clarke, Jamie and Elspie, n.d. (Box 91)
  - Clifton-Taylor, Alec 1964 (Box 91)
  - Cocke, Mr and Mrs., n.d. (Box 91)
  - Cogar, James L. 1963 (Box 91)
  - Coke, Archer 1933 (Box 91)
  - Cooke, Mr. and Mrs. Alistar (Jane) n.d. (Box 91)
  - Cooke, Mrs. Virginia B. 1991 (Box 91)
  - Coolidge, Harold, n.d. (Box 91)
  - Covington, Jane, n.d. 1991 (Box 91)
  - Cousins, Waverly 1968 (Box 91)
  - Cowles, W. Sheffield 1969 (Box 91)
  - Crowell, Mrs. Robert K 1962 and 1967 (Box 91)
  - Dabney, Virginias 1988-1990, 1992, 1995 (Box 91)
  - Daniel, Mrs. Robert Williams (Charlotte Bemiss) 1965 (Box 91)
  - Davie, Mr. and Mrs. Preston 1957 (Box 91)
  - Davis, Samuel III, n.d. 1989-1991 (Box 91)
  - Deane, Frederick, Jr. 1992 (Box 91)
  - Deane, Sir Patrick and Lady August 2, 1966 (Box 91)
  - De La Warr, Lord and Lady, n.d. (Box 91)
  - Dickinson, Harry T., n.d. (Box 91)
  - Douglas, Ned and Jane 1973 (Box 91)
  - Downes, Edward 1960-1962 (Box 91)
  - Dunlop and Helen, n.d. (Box 91)
  - Dunn, Mrs. John Walls 1960-1961 (Box 91)
  - Dunn, William R The Iron Worker1968 (Box 91)
  - Edinger, Valerie 1968 (Box 91)
  - Elicker, Jane Howie Arnold and Family (Mrs. Paul H. Elicker) n.d. 1935, 1938-1939 (Box 91)
  - Eppes, William 1992-1993 (Box 91)
  - Erb, James 1993 (Box 91)
  - Evans, Edward (NED) 1988-1990 (Box 91)
  - Fairburn, Peggy Taylor and Bob 1970-1987 (Box 92)
  - Farwell, Mrs. Albert Day 1967 (Box 92)
  - Finley, David and Margey, n.d. (Box 92)
  - Fischer, Asger and Henni 1967-1968 (Box 92)
  - Fisher, Bruce 1984 (Box 92)
  - Fishers Island Friends 1957 (Box 92)
  - Fistere, John and Isabel 1964 (Box 92)
  - Flexner, James and Beatrice 1965-1968 (Box 92)
  - Ford, Corey 1967 (Box 92)
  - Foreign Friends n.d. (Box 92)
  - Foster, Carmen 1985-1991 (Box 92)
  - Douglas Southall Freeman-Biography Proposal Correspondence (Box 92)
  - Friendly, Pie, n.d. (Box 92)
  - Frisbee, Lucy Putnam Post, n.d. 1990 (Box 92)
  - Fuller, Dick and Betti 1967 (Box 92)
  - Garrett, George 1998 (Box 92)
  - Garrett, Maryle 1956-1988 (Box 92)
  - Gibson 1978 (Box 92)
  - Grappone, Anthony E. (Tony), n.d. (Box 92)
  - Gray, Mrs. Bowman 1971 (Box 92)
  - Greene, Byrd Tucker, n.d. (Box 92)
  - Guest, Virginia 1990 (Box 92)
  - Gummerus, Olaf and Karin 1966 (Box 92)
  - Hagen, Col. Joseph Addison 1968 (Box 92)
  - Hall, Magaret Lee, n.d. 1990-1993 (Box 92)
  - Hamner Family 1988 (Box 92)
  - Hanes, Dewitt 1994 (Box 92)
  - Harrison, B. Powell 1992 (Box 92)
  - Hatch, Henry and Eleanor, n.d. (Box 92)
  - Hechscher, August and Claude 1962 (Box 92)
  - Heim, Francois ET Murka, n.d. (Box 92)
  - Heistand 1970-1972 (Box 92)
  - Hendricks, Kathy Barnes n.d. (Box 92)
  - Hicks, David 1992-1993 (Box 92)
  - Higgins, Billy and Emily 1956-1966 (Box 92)
  - Higgins-Emmy's Wedding 1994 (Box 92)
  - Hofer, Philip 1967-1979 (Box 92)
  - Holland, Ellen 1993 (Box 92)
  - Holmyrad, Mr. and Mrs. Harold 1968-1988, 1991 (Box 92)
  - Hopkins, Evans 1985-1993 (Box 92)
  - Houghton, Amory and Laura 1966 (Box 92)
  - Houghton, Arthur and Betty 1956 (Box 92)
  - Hughes, Mrs. Maria 1979 (Box 92)
  - Iverson, Mrs. Della 1983 (Box 92)
  - Jaffe, Mrs. Louis I. 1992 (Box 92)
  - Jennings, John Melville 1987-1989 (Box 92)
  - Johns, Helen 1991 (Box 92)
  - Johnson, Iris 1934, 1937 (Box 92)
  - Johnson, Nessa 1990-1996 (Box 92)
  - Johnson, Phillip 1967 (Box 92)
  - Johnson, Phillip 1967 (Box 92)
  - Johnston, James 1989-1995 (Box 92)
  - Jones, Ann L. 1991 (Box 92)
  - Jones, Mrs. Harold Massie (Jane) n.d. (Box 92)
  - Karow, Mr. and Mrs. Lester, n.d. (Box 92)
  - Kaster, Robin Sue 1992 (Box 92)
  - Keefer, Lubov B 1953 (Box 92)
  - Keefer, Lubov B 1953 (Box 92)
  - Kiley, Dan 1960 (Box 92)
  - Kirby, James Lewis, n.d. 1991-1995 (Box 92)
  - Kirby, James Lewis (1 of 2) 1996-1997 (Box 92)
  - Kirk, Mrs. Alan 1964-1967 (Box 92)
  - Koch, John 1963 (Box 92)
  - Krock, Arthur 1967 (Box 92)
  - Lanahan, Rosemary, n.d. (Box 92)
  - Leard, John 1991 (Box 92)
  - Lee, Mr. Maurice Dupont 1968-1969 (Box 92)
  - Le Hew, Richard A., D.D.S. Ltd., n.d. 1993 (Box 92)
  - L'Engle, Madeleine (Franklin) 1983-1989 (Box 92)
  - Leonard, Charles and Mrs C. F. (Margery) 1989, 1994 (Box 92)
  - Leonard, Margery A Belikema and Fam. (Mrs. Charles F. Leonard, Jr.) 1935-1936, 1938-1939 (Box 92)
  - Lewis, Lawrence, Jr., n.d. 1988-1992, 1995 (Box 92)
  - Lloyd-Jones, Hannah 1969 (Box 92)
  - Linen, James A., IV 1989 (Box 92)
  - Locker 1968 (Box 92)
  - Logan, Mrs. John A. Jr. (Ann) 1989 (Box 92)
  - Logan, Josh and Netta 1967 (Box 92)
  - Long, Hilary 1991 (Box 92)
  - Lorimer, Linda Koch 1988-1989 (Box 92)
  - Ludgin, Mr. Earle 1968-1969 (Box 92)
  - Macgregor, Elizabeth 1966 (Box 92)
  - Mahoney, Margaret, n.d. (Box 92)
  - Mallon, Mr. and Mrs. Paul 1961-1965 (Box 92)
  - Makepeace, Leroy, n.d. (Box 92)
  - Massie, Margaret, n.d. (Box 92)
  - Martin, Kirby A, Oct 1, 1965 (Box 92)
  - May, Richard A. and Kathleen 1967 (Box 92)
  - Mayes, Judge D. Carleton 1989 (Box 92)
  - McCarthy, William Holladay 1991 (Box 92)
  - McCormick, Thomas J. 1991 (Box 92)
  - Meade, Dr, Roby D 1967, 1968 (Box 92)
  - Mellette, Dr. Susan, n.d. 1982-1983, 1989-1990, 1993-1994 (Box 92)
  - Merrow, Edward L. and Helen 1960 (Box 92)
  - Mielziner, Jo 1966-1967 (Box 92)
  - Miller, Anne F., n.d. 1980 (Box 92)
  - Miller, Betty 1992 (Box 92)
  - Miller, J. Clifford, Jr. n.d. 1957, 1966, 1989-1992, 1995-1998 (Box 92)
  - Milner, Rev Tyler C. 1991-1992 (Box 92)
  - Misc. Correspondence, n.d. 1990-1993 (Box 92)
  - Misc. Newspaper Clippings 1991 (Box 92)
  - Modlin, George, n.d. 1990-1991, 1998 (Box 92)
  - Moore, Dr. Merrill 1964 (Box 92)
  - Moore, Mary Ellen 1994 (Box 92)
  - Morgan, Rodney 1967 (Box 92)
  - Moore, T. Justin, Jr., n.d. 1968, 1989 (Box 92)
  - Morin, Dorothy Liebes and Pat 1958-1964 (Box 92)
  - Morrill, Dr. Richard S., n.d. 1987-1989, 1997 (Box 92)
  - Morris, Mrs. George Maurice (miriam) 1962 (Box 92)
  - Morris, Rose 1955 (Box 92)
  - Morrison, Bill and Patty 1965 (Box 92)
  - Morrison, Julie 1965, 1966 (Box 92)
  - Mudd, Victoria 1966-1968 (Box 92)
  - Murphy, Paul, n.d. 1991-1992 (Box 92)
  - Murrell, Thomas Whitehead III 1990 (Box 92)
  - News Clippings, Richmonders at Woodberry Forest 1930 (Box 92)
  - Nichols, Fredrick D. and Family 1986 (Box 92)
  - Nies-Berger, Edouard 1993 (Box 92)
  - Offenbacker, Miss Birdie C. 1965 (Box 93)